Harris, Raymond and Sara; Papers apap378
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Medical Papers, 1944-2000; 3.6 cubic ft.
  - New York State Assembly - 1982 Committee Bill Memorandum (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - New York State Heart Assembly, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - New York State Heart Assembly - Heartline, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - New York State Heart Assembly Professional and Lady Education Subcommittee of Rehabilitation Committee, 1958-1962 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - New York State Heart Assembly - Professional Education Committee, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - New York State Committee of One Hundred for the Nineteen Hundred Sixty-One White House Conference on Aging - Membership, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - New York State Committee on Tuberculosis and Public Health, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - New York State Department of Social Welfare: Bureau of Disability Determinations, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - New York State Society of Internal Medicine, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - New York State Society of Internal Medicine - Committees, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Northeastern New York Society of Internal Medicine, 1960; 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Notes - Conference and Work (1 of 2), 1963; 1979-1980; 1982; 1986-1987; 1991 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Notes - Conference and Work (2 of 2), 1963; 1979-1980; 1982; 1986-1987; 1991 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Nutritional Problems in Heart Disease, Undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - The Old Heart, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - The Old Heart - Table of Contents, Undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - On Growing Fitter: Time to Shape up, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - On Wisdom and Life - By Raymond Harris, 1969-1970; 1985 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Overcoming the Obstacles to Better Health Care Delivery, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Paper on Endocrine Hypertension, Undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Patient Complaint - RESTRICTED, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - The Periodical Acceleration Tracing in Acute Myocardial Infraction, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Philadelphia Geriatric Center Fifth Annual Awards Banquet, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Photographs Used for Newspaper Articles, 1972; Undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Physical Activity and Aging, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Physical Activity with Aging, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Placid Memorial Hospital - Consultant to the Children's Cardiac Clinic, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Placid Memorial Hospital - Medical Staff, 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Postural Cardiovascular Changes in the Elderly, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - President's Council on Physical Fitness - Silver Anniversary Award, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Promotion-Instructor in Medicine, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Procaine, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Psychosocial Aspects of Cardiovascular Disease, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Raymond Harris - Curriculum Vitae with Medical Publications, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Raymond Harris in the News, 1953-1988 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Reappointment Procedures, 1986; Undated (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Recreational Exercise for Better Health and Longevity, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Rehabilitation of the Geriatric Cardiac Patient, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Rehabilitation of the Geriatric Patient After Coronary Thrombosis, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - The Relationship Between Organic Brain Disease and Physical Status, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Report of Exploratory Talk on Teaching Affiliations, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Reports of Joint Meeting of Editorial Board of the American Journal of Cardiology, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Request For Proposal Rep NHLBI HV-84-2 Systolic Hypertension in the Elderly Program Clinical Centers, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Ronald Reagan and Dr. Harris, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    General
    Glass in folder.
  - Ronald Reagan and Dr. Harris - Copy of Photo, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Saint Joseph's Hospital Health Center School of Nursing, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Saint Peter's Hospital - Committee, 1962; 1967 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Saint Peter's Hospital - Plan Presented at Request of Executive Committee Sub-Department of Cardiology, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Schedule of Dr. Raymond Harris and Arrangements for Coverage - RESTRICTED, 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Schenectady County Agencies Concerned with Rehabilitation of the Mentally Ill and the Retarded, 1963; Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Second William H. Conklin Memorial Lecture, 1980 September 24 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Seniority - Health and Fitness - Getting Fit, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Sense of Smell, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Shock and Syncope, 1968; 1970 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Smoldering Myocarditis with Intermittent Complete A.V Block and Stokes - Adams Syndrome, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Some Observations on Geriatrics as a Specialty, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Special Features Heart Disease in the Elderly Patient, Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Statement of American Medical Association: Re: S.1552. 87th Congress Drug Industry Antitrust, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Statement of Raymond Harris M.D. Concerning the Value of Regular Exercise Programs and activity for Senior Citizens for Presentation, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Stress and Hypertension - Cases - RESTRICTED, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Studies and Clinics - RESTRICTED, 1960-1962; 1964-1965; 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - A Study of Home Conditions and Needs of Older Persons Residing in Public Housing, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Study-Prolonged Procaine Therapy on the Cardiovascular System and Aging Process, Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - SUNY Medical Practice Certificate, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Surgical Medicine: the Geriatric Patient in Elective Surgery: Selection, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Technology For Living, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Temporary State Commission on the Capital City, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Thank You's from Patients - RESTRICTED, 1961; 1973 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Therapeutic Uses of Oral History Techniques, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Times Union Article-Bad Publicity, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Tips on How and When to Manage the Elderly Patient, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Travel Expenses, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Treating the Adolescent Cardiac Patient, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Treatment of Hypertension in Geriatric Patients, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Tuberculosis Association Interview, Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Uihlein Mercy Center, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Unilateral Diaphragmatic Flutter, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - University of Buffalo, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - U.S. Information Return for Calendar Year 1958 - New York State Colleges, Experiment stations, and Extension Associates at Cornell University, Ithaca, New York (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Use of A New Psychic Energizer (Marplan) In An Old Age Home: Double Blind Study, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - View Point: Geriatric Cardiac Rehabilitation, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Vitamins-Minerals-Dianabol-Ritalin, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - When and How to Treat Hypertension in the Aged, 1964; 1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - A Whole Approach to Health, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Working with Older People: A Guide to Practice, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Conferences/Lectures, 1953-2008; 2.4 cubic ft.
  This series contains the conferences and lectures that Raymond and Sara Harris participated in and attended. The conferences and lectures focused on gerontology and cardiovasular health. Both Raymond and Sara Harris gave lectures to members of the medical community, the Gerontological Society of America, and residents of the Albany area. Included in the series are documents from international conferences in Japan, China, Italy, and Israel. These records include travel itineraries, postcards, and souvenirs.
  - 5th World Congress on Physical Activity, Aging, and Sports, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 10th Annual Scientific Sessions of the Society of Geriatric Cardiology, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 14th Annual Meeting of the American Geriatrics Society, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 25th Annual Meeting of the Gerontological Society, 1972; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 27th Annual Meeting - American Geriatrics Society - RESTRICTED, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 36th Annual Scientific Session - Computerized Office Management, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 50th Anniversary Celebration of the Gerontology Society of America, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1997 International Conference on Aging and Physical Activity (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Acute Myocardial Infarction in the Aged: Prognosis and Management, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Adult Learning Institute Day, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Advances in the Diagnosis and Treatment of Older People - A New Look at Old Age, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Age and Prognosis of Patients with Acute Myocardial Infraction, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Aging, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Aging and the Heart - Saratoga County Heart Chapter, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Aging is a Life Long Process, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - AMA Conference on Long-Term Care, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - American College of Cardiology Clinical Workshop Program, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - American Medical Association Conference - The Relationship of Physical Activity and Mental Health, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - American Orthopsychiatric Association, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - An International Directory of Gerontological Organizations, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Annual Business Meeting of the New York State Heart Assembly ,Inc., 1965; Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Assessing and Preparing Heart Patients for a Return to a Meaningful Life, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Biennial National Convention - National Jewish Welfare Board, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bioethical Considerations for the Use of Medical Devices and Instrumentation for the Elderly, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Blindness and Aging, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - British Cardiac Society, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Cardiology and Aging - First International Erlangen-Nurnberg Symposium on Experimental Gerontology, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Cardiology of Aging - An Entity or Amalgamation - A Symposium on the Cardiology of Aging, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Cardiovascular Rehabilitation: The Role of the New York State Heart Assembly, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Cardiovascular Update - Fifteenth Annual Cardiovascular Teaching Day, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - The Catholic Church in the Health Field, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Chautauqua, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Chronic Conditions and Activity Limitations, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Columbia University Students and Ann Lee Home Program, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Conference Confirmations, 1967; 1981; Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Conference of Voluntary National Organizations, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Conference on Medical Device Technology, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Conference on Medical Education and Research - Research Program Belongs in the Hospital, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Deutchen Gesellshaft Fur Gerontologie - Ventricular Arrhythias in Old Age - Therapeutic Considerations, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - El Comite Organizador Del IV Congresso Mundial De Cardiologia, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Eleventh Annual Meeting of the Gerontological Society, Inc., 1958 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Eleventh International Congress of Gerontology (1 of 4), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Eleventh International Congress of Gerontology (2 of 4), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Eleventh International Congress of Gerontology (3 of 4), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Eleventh International Congress of Gerontology (4 of 4), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Fifth Annual Southern Conference on Gerontology/Seventh Annual Scientific Meeting of the Gerontology Society, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - First Annual Rehabilitation on the Cardiac Child, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - First Appalachian Conference on Physical Activity and Aging, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - First International Congress on Patient Counseling, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - First National Conference on Physical Fitness and Sports for All, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - For the Health of IT, 2006-2007; Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Foundation of the New York State Nurse Association, Undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - The Franklin Corporation, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Geriatric Cardiology - Physiologic vs. Pathologic Aging of the Cardiovascular System: Clinical Applications and Therapeutic Considerations, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Geriatric Depression Conference, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Geriatric Medicine - Regional Medical Program, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Geriatric Specialty Conference, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Gerontological Society - 28th Annual Scientific Meeting, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Gerontologist - Program House Meeting, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Gerontology, Geriatrics, and the Primary Care Physician, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Gerontology Lecture at the University of Buffalo, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Gerontology Society Program - 24th Annual Meeting, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Gerontology Tours, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Goals of Medical and Psychological Care of the Aged, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Health and Services Fair, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Health of All Peoples: A Question of Human Values, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Healthcare and the Elderly: Education the Future Professional, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - The Heart Association of Southeastern Pennsylvania - The Application of Computers in Cardiovascular Disease, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Heart Diseases in Business and Industry Employment Problems Affecting Cardiac Patients, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Hebrew Rehabilitation Center for the Aged, 1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - History of Medicine Society - Encounters With Cultural Revolutions; Experiences of a Medical Writer, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Holiarity - The Fourth Phase of Medicine, 1954-1957; 1962 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Homes For the Aged in Sweden Offer Ideas for Americans, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - How to Develop An Abiding Environment for Senior Citizens Through New York States Housing Programs, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - ICHPER-SD 38th World Congress Symposium on Aging Format, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Independent Living For Older People, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Institute for Physical Fitness - Bonnie Prudden, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Institute on Geriatrics, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Institute on Medicine - Committee on Aging and Medical Education, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - International Conference on Aging and Physical Activity, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - International Conference on "Recent Advances in Care of the Elderly", 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - International Congresses/Conferences on Physical Activity, Aging, and Sports, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Issues in the History of Aging and in the History of Gerontology, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - John M. Dorsey, 1957; 1971; Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Leadership When Lecturing, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Lecture for Albany Medical Students, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Leisure Time and Exercise Activities for the Elderly, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - The LENS Program Linking Education, Nurses, Seniors - Focusing on Health and Wellness, Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Lifelong Learning: The Seventh Annual Oxford/Berkeley Program, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Long Term Care, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Longitudinal Studies of Adulthood and Aging: Their Past and Implications for the Future, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Managing Delusions and Irrational Behavior, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Maximizing the Assets of Aging with Good Health Care and Fitness - News Clip, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Medical and Nursing Aspects of Geriatric Cardiac Rehabilitation, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Medical Society of New York State - 160th Annual Convention, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Medical Supervision of Nursing Home Patients, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Mount Saint Mary College - Lecture on Technology and Medicine: Clinical and Ethical Imperatives, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Mental Health Issues, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - National Graduate University -Improving the Quality of Life in Late Years with Special Regard to Friendship, Love, Marriage, and Sex, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - National Institute on Aging, Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - National Jewish Welfare Board Biennial Convention, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - National Leadership Conference on Physical Activity and Women's Health, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - National Leadership Training Institute - Albany - A Community in Progress, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - New Medical Horizons in Aging, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - New York State Department of Health and the Department of Health Intra-Agency Task Force on Women's Issues, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - New York State Medical Society Symposium, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - New York State Moreland Act Commission on Nursing Homes and Residential Facilities, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Nursing Home Administration-Columbia University, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Nursing Homes Symposium, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Ollie A. Randall Award Banquet, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Panels, Undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Physical Activity and Cardiovascular Problems of the Elderly, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Post-Graduate Seminars in Geriatric Medicine - Ann Lee Home, 1953; 1965 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - The President's Council on Physical Fitness and Sports - The National Conference on Fitness and Aging, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Proceedings of Annual Conference "Serving the Aging Blind", 1960 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Progress Report on Research of the Rehabilitation Field Laboratory, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Progressive Resistance Exercises for the Elderly, Undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Realities of Physical and Mental Aging, Undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Rehabilitation for the Hemiplegic, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Rehabilitation of Stroke Patients - Thank You, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Renovascular Disease - Lecture at St. Peter's, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - The Right to Health in Old Age, 1960; 1962 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Second Annual Capital Distinct Conference on Aging, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Selecting the Marco-Projects Most Conductive to a Secure, Prosperous and Healthy National Future: An Achilles Heel in the Prevailing Approach to Management Science?, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Senior Citizen's Festival, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Sixth International Congress on Gerontology/Europe Trip, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - SnowFish LLC, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Society of Geriatric Cardiology 14th Annual Scientific Session, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - The Socio-Economic Aspects of Arthritis-Response, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Special Feature of Heart Disease-Maimonides Hospital, Undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - State of New York-Office of Aging, Undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - State Society on Aging of New York, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Statement of Raymond Harris, M.D. Concerning the Value of Regular Exercise Programs and Activity for Senior Citizens for Presentation, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Sterling-Winthrop Research Institute, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Steven F. Windmueller Talk, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Symposium on Aging and the Brain, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Talk at Colonie Library Hearing, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Team Approach to the Evaluation of the Cardiac Patient Using a Cardiac Work Evaluation Clinic, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Tenth International Congress of Gerontology (1 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Tenth International Congress of Gerontology (2 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Tenth International Congress of Gerontology (3 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Third World Congress of Pediatric Cardiology, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Three Days of Cardiology, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Twelfth World Rehabilitation Congress, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - "Worlds of a Doctor" - Albany Public Library, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - W. Alton Jones Cell Science Center, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Vith Asia-Pacific Congress on Diseases of the Chest in Bombay Announcement, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Center for the Study of Aging, 1952-2009; 4.3 cubic ft.
  This series contains documents related to the Center for the Study of Aging opened by Raymond and Sara Harris. Sara Harris, who was the executive director of the center, was active in the senior community in Albany, N.Y. Located on Madison Avenue, the Center for the Study of Aging provided programs, lectures, and a community space for the senior community. Included in the series are documents related to the founding of the center, program events, correspondence related to the center, information about its non-profit status, and articles and news clips related to the events that the center hosted. The series also includes published books written by Sara Harris and other members of the gerontology community, as well as publications relating to the center's findings and activities.
  - 27th Annual Meeting - American Geriatrics Society, 1970 (Box 1, Cassette 1)
  - 40th Anniversary Bio's and C.V.'s, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 40th Anniversary Party - Photos, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 45th Anniversary Celebration, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1974-1975 Psychiatric Aspects of Mobility (Box 1, Cassette 2)
  - 2001 W. Va Conference Rural (Oversized 1, Floppy-disk 1)
  - AARP - Volunteer Opportunities, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Active Aging in the New Millennium, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Aging and Disease, 1981 May 18 (Box 1, Cassette 3)
  - Agreement Between the Lawrence Frankel Foundation of Charleston West Virginia and the CSA, 1994; Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agreement Between Olga Hurley and CSA - RESTRICTED, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alternatives to Institutionalization of the Elderly, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Anita Harris - WRFM Radio Programs on Aging, 1975-1976; Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Archives and Oral History Project, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Arthur Neulander (Dr.): The Geriatric Day Care Center, Undated (1-inch type c 2)
  - Backup File System, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Minicartridge 1)
  - Barbara Doyle, Undated (1-inch type c 1)
  - Barnes and Noble Book Information, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - A Basic Socio-Medical Design for Community Research in Aging, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bibliographic Reference, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Billing Holistic Fund, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Board Liability Insurance, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors, 1998-2001; 2004 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors' Meeting Minutes, 1972-2006 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Book and Tape Order Form, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Book Buyers, 2003; 2007 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Book Inventories (1 of 2), 1995-1999; 2001; 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Book Inventories (2 of 2), 1995-1999; 2001; 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Book Order Forms, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Book Royalties, 1999; 2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Break Your Work Habits, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Bylaws, 1988; 1999 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Bylaws Changes, 1999-2000; 2002-2003; 2006 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Center of Aging (1 of 15), 2005 September (Box 2, Mini-dv 1)
  - Center of Aging (2 of 15), 2005 September (Box 2, Mini-dv 2)
  - Center of Aging (3 of 15), 2005 September (Box 2, Mini-dv 3)
  - Center of Aging (4 of 15), 2005 September (Box 2, Mini-dv 4)
  - Center of Aging (5 of 15), 2005 September (Box 2, Mini-dv 5)
  - Center of Aging (6 of 15), 2005 September (Box 2, Mini-dv 6)